Jeremy Alexander

9935 SW Pimlico Terrace Beaverton, OR, 97008 (503) 707-0623

<u>Imalexander29@gmail.com</u>

http://www.jeremyalexander.webhostingforstudents.com/

Summary of Qualifications:

Background in assisting the general public by providing clerical work, patron security and the overall supervision of facilities.

Web design experience with gathering requirements, research, project management and user-based design concepts to write HTML and CSS web pages to display accurately on any device that supports web functionality.

Experience in front end web development using HTML5, CSS3 (LESS), JavaScript, and CMS.

Search Engine Optimization including on-page and off-page keyword density, meta data research and analysis, traffic generation, online tools and SEO software.

Ability to optimize website content properties and styles for a mobile first design, using progressive enhancement for larger resolutions.

Proficient with current office standards, systems, and applications.

Education:

Web Design program, Portland Community College, Portland, OR- (Fall 2012- present) Southridge High School, Beaverton, OR – (Class of 2010)

Work Experience:

Evening and Weekend Supervisor, After School Club Leader, Sports Instructor, Tualatin Hills Park and Recreation District, Portland, OR (Oct.2015-present)

- Assist general public by providing clerical work, patron security and the overall supervision of the facility
- Maintain program attendance records and data entry in the district database
- Prepare and implement daily lesson plans for programs and classes
- Plan, coordinate, and lead large-group activities while maintaining a safe and productive environment
- Drove the district parks and recreation vans and buses

Inventory Associate, Best Buy, Beaverton, OR (Oct. 2011- Dec 2013)

- Prepare and fulfill online and in-store customer orders
- Routinely maintained a clean and safe warehouse by performing weekly safety checklists and building security
- Prepare, proofread, and audited a variety of bill of lading forms, invoices, receipts, and labels

Jeremy Alexander

9935 SW Pimlico Terrace Beaverton, OR, 97008 (503) 707-0623

<u>Jmalexander29@gmail.com</u> <u>http://www.jeremyalexander.webhostingforstudents.com/</u>

- Assisted project teams with store planograms and transformations
- Efficient shipping and receiving procedures while processing freight

Supervisor, Jamba Juice, Tigard, OR (Apr.2010- Jan 2012)

- Facilitated improvements towards team building, supervision, quality work relationships through meetings and trainings
- Maintained, counted, and replenished inventory levels on a weekly basis
- Handled cash and audited paperwork for the store

Team Member, Rainier Roasters, Tigard, OR (Jun. 2009- Jan. 2010)

- Assisted with store deliveries, and participated in general store maintenance
- Prep work, cooking, and serving orders to guests

Volunteer Experience:

P.A.L-Police Activities League, Beaverton, OR (2009-2010)

- Assisted P.A.L staff by setting up activities, games, and tracked activity logs
- Participated in games, activities, and gatherings with the group
- Guided students through various homework assignments

<u>Licenses, Certificates and Other Requirements</u>

Current CPR/AED/First-Aid certification